<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<SmellBaseline>
  <ManuallySuppressedIssues/>
  <CurrentIssues>
    <ID>ComplexCondition:HttpClientFactory.kt:HttpClientFactory$requestTokens != null &amp;&amp; access != null &amp;&amp; refresh != null &amp;&amp; (access != requestTokens.accessToken || refresh != requestTokens.refreshToken)</ID>
    <ID>CyclomaticComplexMethod:HttpClientFactory.kt:HttpClientFactory$fun createAuthenticatedClient: HttpClient</ID>
    <ID>LargeClass:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder</ID>
    <ID>MagicNumber:HttpClientFactory.kt:HttpClientFactory$400</ID>
    <ID>MagicNumber:HttpClientFactory.kt:HttpClientFactory$401</ID>
    <ID>MagicNumber:HttpClientFactory.kt:HttpClientFactory$403</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"+1: Draw a card. At the beginning of the next end step, untap two lands.\n-3: Put target nonland permanent into its owner's library third from the top.\n-8: You get an emblem with \"Whenever you draw a card, exile target permanent an opponent controls.\""</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"+1: Draw a card. At the beginning of the next end step, untap two lands.\n−3: Put target nonland permanent into its owner's library third from the top.\n−8: You get an emblem with \"Whenever you draw a card, exile target permanent an opponent controls.\""</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"+1: Each player discards a card.\n-2: Target player sacrifices a creature.\n-6: Separate all permanents target player controls into two piles. That player sacrifices all permanents in the pile of their choice."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"+2: Look at the top card of target player's library, you may put that card on the bottom of that player's library.\n"</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"+2: Look at the top card of target player's library, you may put that card on the bottom of that player's library.\n0: Draw three cards, then put two cards from your hand on top of your library in any order.\n-1: Return target creature to its owner's hand.\n-12: Exile all cards from target player's library, then that player shuffles their hand into their library."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"+2: Ugin, the Spirit Dragon deals 3 damage to any target.\n- X: Exile each permanent with converted mana cost X or less that's one or more colors.\n-10: You gain 7 life, draw seven cards, then put up to seven permanent cards from your hand onto the battlefield."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"+4: Target player exiles a card from their hand.\n-3: Exile target permanent.\n-14: Restart the game, leaving in exile all non-Aura permanents exiled with Karn Liberated."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"-12: Exile all cards from target player's library, then that player shuffles their hand into their library."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"0: Draw three cards, then put two cards from your hand on top of your library in any order.\n"</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"As Cavern of Souls enters the battlefield, choose a creature type. {T}: Add {C}. {T}: Add one mana of any color. Spend this mana only to cast a creature spell of the chosen type, and that spell can't be countered."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"At the beginning of your upkeep, reveal the top card of your library and put that card into your hand. You lose life equal to its converted mana cost."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"At the beginning of your upkeep, reveal the top card of your library and put that card into your hand. You lose life equal to its mana value."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"At the beginning of your upkeep, you may put a charge counter on Aether Vial. {T}: You may put a creature card with converted mana cost equal to the number of charge counters on Aether Vial from your hand onto the battlefield."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Bloodghast can't block. Bloodghast has haste as long as an opponent has 10 or less life. Landfall — Whenever a land enters the battlefield under your control, you may return Bloodghast from your graveyard to the battlefield."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Choose one — Counter target spell; or draw two cards; or gain control of target nonland permanent with converted mana cost 1 or less."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Choose two — Counter target spell; or return target permanent to its owner's hand; or tap all creatures your opponents control; or draw a card."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Counter target spell. If that spell is countered this way, put it into its owner's hand instead of that player's graveyard. Draw a card."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Destroy target creature if it has converted mana cost 2 or less. Revolt — Destroy that creature if it has converted mana cost 4 or less instead if a permanent you controlled left the battlefield this turn."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Draw a card if an opponent has cast a blue or black spell this turn. Spells you control can't be countered this turn; you and permanents you control gain hexproof from blue and from black until end of turn."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Engineered Explosives enters the battlefield with X charge counters on it. {2}, Sacrifice Engineered Explosives: Destroy each nonland permanent with converted mana cost equal to the number of charge counters on Engineered Explosives."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Equipped creature gets +2/+2 and has protection from red and from blue. Whenever equipped creature deals combat damage to a player, Sword of Fire and Ice deals 2 damage to any target and you draw a card."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Exile target creature. Its controller may search their library for a basic land card, put that card onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Field of the Dead enters the battlefield tapped. Whenever Field of the Dead or another land enters the battlefield under your control, if you control seven or more lands with different names, create a 2/2 black Zombie creature token."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Flash, flying. Brazen Borrower can block only creatures with flying. Adventure — Petty Theft: Return target nonland permanent an opponent controls to its owner's hand."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Flash, flying. When Restoration Angel enters the battlefield, you may exile target non-Angel creature you control, then return that card to the battlefield under your control."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Flash, flying. When Vendilion Clique enters the battlefield, look at target player's hand. You may choose a nonland card from it. If you do, that player puts that card on the bottom of their library, then draws a card."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Flash. When Snapcaster Mage enters the battlefield, target instant or sorcery card in your graveyard gains flashback until end of turn."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Haste. Whenever Goblin Guide attacks, defending player reveals the top card of their library. If it's a land card, that player puts it into their hand."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Hexproof. Lotus Field enters the battlefield tapped. When Lotus Field enters the battlefield, sacrifice two lands. {T}: Add three mana of any one color."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"If Leyline of the Void is in your opening hand, you may begin the game with it on the battlefield. If a card would be put into an opponent's graveyard from anywhere, exile it instead."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"If it's not your turn, you may exile a blue card from your hand rather than pay this spell's mana cost. Counter target noncreature spell. If that spell is countered this way, exile it instead of putting it into its owner's graveyard."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Imprint — When Isochron Scepter enters the battlefield, you may exile an instant card with converted mana cost 2 from your hand. {2}, {T}: You may copy the exiled card. If you do, you may cast the copy without paying its mana cost."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Imprint — When Isochron Scepter enters the battlefield, you may exile an instant card with converted mana cost 2 or less from your hand. {2}, {T}: You may copy the exiled card. If you do, you may cast the copy without paying its mana cost."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Lifelink. When Murderous Rider dies, put it on the bottom of its owner's library. Adventure — Swift End: Destroy target creature or planeswalker. You lose 2 life."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Sacrifice Sakura-Tribe Elder: Search your library for a basic land card, put that card onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Target player reveals their hand. You choose a nonland card from it. That player discards that card. You lose 2 life."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Tarmogoyf's power is equal to the number of card types among cards in all graveyards and its toughness is that number plus 1."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"This spell can't be countered. When you cast Emrakul, take an extra turn after this one. Flying, protection from colored spells, annihilator 6. When Emrakul is put into a graveyard from anywhere, its owner shuffles their graveyard into their library."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"This spell can't be countered. When you cast Emrakul, take an extra turn after this one. Flying, protection from colored spells, annihilator 6. When Emrakul is put into the graveyard from anywhere, its owner shuffles their graveyard into their library."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"This spell costs {2} less to cast if it targets a blue spell. Counter target spell unless its controller pays {3}."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Trample. Whenever Primeval Titan enters the battlefield or attacks, you may search your library for up to two land cards, put them onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Walking Ballista enters the battlefield with X +1/+1 counters. {4}: Put a +1/+1 counter on Walking Ballista. Remove a +1/+1 counter: It deals 1 damage to any target."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"When Agent of Treachery enters the battlefield, gain control of target permanent. At the beginning of your end step, if you control three or more permanents you don't own, draw three cards."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"When Avenger of Zendikar enters the battlefield, create a 0/1 green Plant creature token for each land you control. Landfall — Whenever a land enters the battlefield under your control, put a +1/+1 counter on each Plant creature you control."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"When Eternal Witness enters the battlefield, you may return target card from your graveyard to your hand."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"When Rest in Peace enters the battlefield, exile all graveyards. If a card or token would be put into a graveyard from anywhere, exile it instead."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"When Thought-Knot Seer enters the battlefield, target opponent reveals their hand. You choose a nonland card from it. That player exiles that card. When it leaves the battlefield, target opponent draws a card."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"When Thragtusk enters the battlefield, you gain 5 life. When Thragtusk leaves the battlefield, create a 3/3 green Beast creature token."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"When Uro enters the battlefield, sacrifice it unless it escaped. Whenever Uro enters the battlefield or attacks, you gain 3 life and draw a card, then you may put a land card from your hand onto the battlefield. Escape—{GG}{UU}, Exile five other cards from your graveyard."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"When you cast this spell, you gain half X life and draw half X cards, rounded down each time. Flying, trample."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Whenever Inferno Titan enters the battlefield or attacks, it deals 3 damage divided as you choose among one, two, or three targets."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"Whenever equipped creature deals combat damage, put two charge counters on Umezawa's Jitte. Remove a charge counter: Choose one — Equipped creature gets +2/+2 until end of turn; Or target creature gets -1/-1 until end of turn; Or gain 2 life."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"You may pay 1 life and exile a blue card from your hand rather than paying this spell's mana cost."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"You may return an Island you control to its owner's hand rather than pay Daze's mana cost. Counter target spell unless its controller pays {1}."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{1}: Look at the top three cards of your library, then put them back in any order. {T}: Draw a card, then put Sensei's Divining Top on top of its owner's library."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{1}{G/P}, {T}, Sacrifice a creature: Search your library for a creature card with converted mana cost equal to 1 plus the sacrificed creature's converted mana cost, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle your library."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{G}: Exile target card from a graveyard. If it was a creature card, put a +1/+1 counter on Scavenging Ooze and you gain 1 life."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{T}, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Scalding Tarn: Search your library for an Island or Mountain card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle your library."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{T}, Pay 1 life, Sacrifice Wooded Foothills: Search your library for a Mountain or Forest card, put it onto the battlefield, then shuffle."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{T}, Sacrifice Fabled Passage: Search your library for a basic land card, put it onto the battlefield tapped, then shuffle. Then if you control four or more lands, untap that land."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{T}: Add {C}. {1}: Inkmoth Nexus becomes a 1/1 Blinkmoth artifact creature with flying and infect until end of turn. It's still a land."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{T}: Add {W} or {U}. {3}{W}{U}: Until end of turn, Celestial Colonnade becomes a 4/4 white and blue Elemental creature with flying and vigilance. It's still a land."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{T}: Choose target artifact a player controls and target artifact card in that player's graveyard. If both targets are still legal as this ability resolves, that player simultaneously sacrifices the artifact and returns the artifact card to the battlefield."</ID>
    <ID>MaxLineLength:BrowseCatalogSeeder.kt:BrowseCatalogSeeder$"{T}: Exile target land card from a graveyard. Add one mana of any color.\n{B}, {T}: Exile target instant or sorcery card from a graveyard. Each opponent loses 2 life.\n{G}, {T}: Exile target creature card from a graveyard. You gain 2 life."</ID>
    <ID>ReturnCount:BrowseCardRemoteMediator.kt:BrowseCardRemoteMediator$override suspend fun load: MediatorResult</ID>
    <ID>ReturnCount:UserRepositoryImpl.kt:UserRepositoryImpl$override suspend fun getSession: UserSession?</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:BrowseCardRemoteMediator.kt:BrowseCardRemoteMediator$e: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:RunIoResult.kt:e: Exception</ID>
    <ID>TooGenericExceptionCaught:SafeApiCall.kt:e: Exception</ID>
  </CurrentIssues>
</SmellBaseline>
